让我们来讨论讨论  说真的  这个是根据你的数据大小
Let's talk about this. Honestly, it really depends on
来决定的  对于储存量小的
the size of your data. For small amounts of
二进制数据  那些小到不用操心的那种
binary data, very, very small amounts of binary data,
你只需要把原始数据放进
you could actually put the raw data in the
数据库  有一小部分的数据是这样类型的  而且这些数据的储存
database. There are blob types and those are supported
功能工作的很好  当然了  如果你打算把
and work pretty well. However, as you start putting
大一点的数据放进数据库  这种原始数据储存就不实用了
larger data into the database, it gets pretty inefficient.
你就不得不写一大堆程序来解决这个问题
And you end up writing a lot more code.
当然  只要是把数据储存在设备的公共文件夹
Well, as far as storing the files in a public folder
这些都要考虑以上问题  当然  上述的方法还是可以解决问题的  只要
on the device is concerned, well, that might work if you
你想把文件分享出去  但是  事实上  你不想让这些文件跟
actually wanted to share those files. But, typically, you don't want to
别的应用的文件混在一起  所以把这些文件放在公共
share those files with other applications. So, storing them in a
文件夹是一个坏主意  除此之外  第三个
public folder on the device isn't a very good idea. But
选择其实也挺好  把这些文件储存在一个
the third option is pretty good. Storing the files in a
私人的文件夹同时在参照一个数据库中的地址  这是
private folder and then referencing the location in the database. Now,
无可厚非的  你就不需要把温泉全部放在数据库了
admittedly, you might not even need to put them into the database
不过这通常值得去做如果
at all. But it's often nice to do this if
你需要做一系列的查询  你
you need to do any kind of queries on them. You
可以把元始数据储存在数据库并且储存在
can store metadata in the database and store files in
私有文件夹  这就是安卓gallery文件廊如何工作的
a private folder. This is what Android does in the gallery.